'use strict';

const QUESTIONDATA = [{
    questionID: 1,
    question: '¿Qué onda?',
    choices: ['What\'s your name?', 'Where is the bathroom?', 'Really? / For real?', 'What\'s up?'],
    answer: 'What\'s up?'
  },
  {
    questionID: 2,
    question: '¿Mande?',
    choices: ['What? / Tell me / Go ahead', 'What\'s up?', 'Really? / For real?', 'Do you know?'],
    answer: 'What? / Tell me / Go ahead'
  },
  {
    questionID: 3,
    question: '¡No manches!',
    choices: ['Cast the devil out!', 'No worries!', 'No way! / Come on!', 'Bananas!'],
    answer: 'No way! / Come on!'
  },
  {
    questionID: 4,
    question: '¿Neta?',
    choices: ['Banana?', 'Really? / For real?', 'Do you know?', 'Where is it?'],
    answer: 'Really? / For real?'
  },
  {
    questionID: 5,
    question: 'Ni modo',
    choices: ['Slang for banana', 'That\'s neat', 'Me too', 'No matter / It can’t be helped'],
    answer: 'No matter / It can’t be helped'
  },
  {
    questionID: 6,
    question: 'Chido',
    choices: ['Cool', 'A short child', 'Tortilla chips', 'Dinner'],
    answer: 'Cool'
  },
  {
    questionID: 7,
    question: 'Crudo',
    choices: ['Cruddy', 'Happy', 'Lost', 'Hung over'],
    answer: 'Hung over'
  },
  {
    questionID: 8,
    question: 'Cochino',
    choices: ['Truck / Car', 'Dirty / Disgusting / Rude', 'Train', 'Person who is cool'],
    answer: 'Dirty / Disgusting / Rude'
  },
  {
    questionID: 9,
    question: 'Chela',
    choices: ['Cheese', 'Dress', 'Beer', 'Banana'],
    answer: 'Beer'
  },
  {
    questionID: 10,
    question: 'Chiste',
    choices: ['Joke / Trick', 'Spill', 'Drunk', 'Lost'],
    answer: 'Joke / Trick'
  }
];